[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Mr. Fang!
Dantian, Dantian, Dantian.
He's awake.
Are you hungry? Are you cold?
Do you feel uncomfortable anywhere?
Mr. Fang, why are you sleeping on the floor?
Well, this bed is too soft.
It's uncomfortable to sleep on.
One for each of us.
I don't smoke.
Mr. Fang, a lighter is no use to me.
A lighter is one of those things...
that seems useless,
but when you need it and don't have it,
it's really frustrating.
I bought this ages ago.
I've been waiting for you.
Didn't dare touch it. Saved it just for you.
Dig in.
Oh my god.
Tastes like heaven, doesn't it?
So good.
A bit dry, right?
This is true art. What is art?
This is art.
So, Mr. Fang,
how did we get here?
You've been out for a day.
I was out that long?
The doctor gave you an anti-inflammatory shot.
Your leg will be fine by tomorrow.
Mr. Fang.
The cup Rong Sihai gave me...
I left it in the cave.
The books you gave me all burned, too. It's a shame.
I'll buy you a new cup.
I didn't burn all the books.
Don't be afraid of failure
There's always hope
"What is Success"
By Fang Haowen
Don't mind what others think
You're actually not stupid at all
Wishing you a baby soon
Your close friend, Fang Haowen
Why are there two extra lines?
I just wrote this new part.
And let me tell you,
I didn't write the first part.
Mr. Fang.
Hey, let's wait in line.
Here's the thing.
My son is a bit special.
I'd like to ask Mr. Fang
to write him a few more encouraging words.
That's your son?
Growing up to be this big is already a huge success for your son.
Stop keeping Mr. Fang
from inspiring everyone else.
So many people are waiting to be inspired.
No, uh...
Just... go back.
All signed.
Thank you, Mr. Fang.
Borrowing this.
Why are you taking my pen?
Thank you.
Son.
Mr. Fang signed it for you.
Take a look.
That's a big win, right?
Don't be afraid.
Failure hope will always be there.
You need to watch your phrasing.
Don't be afraid of failure.
Hope is always there.
Mr. Fang.
Thank you, Mr. Fang.
You're a good guy.
Eat up.
I'll take you to the police station later.
And then we'll take a walk around Tiananmen.
Okay.
You're awake.
Bie Fan.
Bie Fan!
Sihai!
How come you're awake?
You... why are you here?
I've been waiting for you all day.
I just went down for some fruit and you woke up.
I've been looking for you for two months.
You even made it on TV.
You looked for me for two months?
Then what did you even eat?
Food, obviously.
I know.
I figured. I just knew.
I knew you'd look for me. Given our bond.
Given our bond.
Hurry, Sihai.
Have a seat, have a seat.
Okay.
Make yourself at home.
I miss your cooking.
Don't even mention it.
I miss your cooking too.
When you were gone,
my cooking always felt like...
Wang Yue.
I can't put my finger on it.
I knew you'd come looking for me.
You've been looking for over two months, huh?
Oh my god.
Wait, if you're looking for me, what about your husband?
Where is your husband?
Right here!
Who are you?
Fang Haowen!
Haozi!
I knew you weren't dead!
Mr. Fang!
What brings you here?
We got here yesterday!
After we got married,
we had to host a reception at Wang Yue's place, right?
We arrived yesterday.
The reception is tomorrow.
But she said her stomach felt a bit off,
so I got worried
and rushed her to the hospital
for a proper checkup.
I didn't expect
such a coincidence
to bump into our great matchmaker, Mr. Fang!
My hand! My hand's hurt! My hand!
No, no, no, my bad!
Are you okay?
Reception.
Arrived yesterday.
What a coincidence.
Honey,
I'll go grab a smoke then.
You two catch up. Catch up.
Mr. Fang,
you really are...
so warmhearted.
Didn't you say
that writers who smoke
are empty-headed?
I don't smoke.
I just simply like fire.
Seeing you here really is a coincidence, huh.
Coincidence my ass.
I refused to believe you were dead.
I told Zhao En
to come back and see you.
Just in case you weren't dead.
Guess that "in case" came true, huh.
Sit.
Seeing you
is so great. I'm absolutely ecstatic.
Sorry, sorry! Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
Alright, you're the educated one.
I can't eat anymore.
I'm pregnant.
I was wondering...
...if the baby and I...
With you?
With me...
What's it got to do with you?
...share the same zodiac sign?
Weren't you born in February?
This baby is due in August.
Unbelievable. You held that in just to ask about zodiac signs?
One more thing.
That night with Jin Furong...
Nothing happened at all.
I haven't dated anyone else since you.
I know there's no point in saying this.
But I just wanted to tell you, you know?
Okay.
Got it.
Thanks, I guess.
Well, at your age...
Shouldn't you find someone too?
You're not exactly a looker...
You're getting older...
Your health probably isn't great...
And you have a bad temper.
Don't I have any good qualities?
You're a decent person.
Nothing good about my looks?
You're a really decent person.
Then set me up with someone.
Okay.
I'll keep that in mind.
It's almost time.
I'm gonna go see if he's done smoking.
I'm off.
Yue'er.
Wishing you a happy marriage!
Wishing you happiness every day.
Hello, excuse me.
Is there any hot water here?
There's a dispenser in the water room. Help yourself.
What book are you reading?
"I 'Have No' Talent"
Written by Fang Haowen.
I haven't even published it yet.
Just hit the shelves. Hard to find.
You haven't read this book?
This guy is incredibly talented.
Just died too young.
He's dead?
Yeah, he's dead.
So do you think the book is good?
It's really deep.
Really hard to understand.
But it grows on you the more you read.
It's a poetry collection.
It's super interesting.
Such a shame.
Look at this Fang Haowen...
Blew up after he died.
Number one trending every day.
What do you mean, trending?
Take a look. Number one.
Tomorrow, Huanxi City will hold
a grand Fang Haowen
memorial service.
Why are you here?
Fang.
I was worried something might happen to you.
So I came along with you.
Then why are you here?
I was worried something might happen to him.
So I followed him here.
And why are you here?
He's asking you.
Standing ticket. Just leaning to rest.
Mr. Fang, wait for me!
You're really talented.
Mr. Fang!
You were my pillar of strength!
Your sewer owes Fang Haowen an apology!
Your manhole cover hurt Mr. Fang!
Excuse me.
Is this where Mr. Fang Haowen fell in?
I don't know where he fell in.
I just got transferred here.
Alright, it's confirmed, guys.
This is exactly where Mr. Fang Haowen fell in.
Come on, let's take a closer look.
Hi everyone, I'm Fang Haowen's landlord.
I know you all feel bad for him.
But have some pity on me, too!
Stop sending things, there's already so much!
The first week of mourning has already passed!
My dearest Wen,
As I stand here today,
my heart is immensely heavy and full of pain.
Yes,
I know you're gone,
but I still
can't believe it's real.
I remember when we first met.
In your eyes,
there was a sorrow that didn't belong in this world.
So quiet,
like an unfinished epic.
Even though we once had
our misunderstandings and arguments.
Even though you once chose to leave.
I could never forget
the warmth you gave me.
Because,
I love you.
I will keep you forever
in the deepest part of my heart.
May you rest in peace.
That was so... so touching.
Darling, that was amazing.
Great.
Okay, thanks. Thanks.
Who wrote that speech for me?
That totally grossed me out.
An AI wrote it. It's an auto-generated text.
Don't blame everything on AI.
No, it worked really well!
The crew down there were wiping away tears.
Were they crying for real?
Weren't they crying because it was so gross?
You made me say that gross stuff just to sell books?
Seriously, He Jiahuan.
No...
Mr. Ethan,
after you.
Let me introduce you two.
This is the boss of Sandao Underwear,
Mr. Ethan.
And this is from the publicly listed Furong Group,
Jin Furong, CEO Jin.
CEO Jin, nice to meet you.
Your little company
is doing quite well.
Hey, Mike,
add this... this...
underwear boss on WeChat.
Okay, darling.
"Underwear."
Uh... well...
Mr. Ethan.
Ethan.
CEO Jin.
Go ahead.
When is our underwear getting listed on the stream today?
If it doesn't go up soon, our boss will kill me.
After all, our brand paid the most.
Go ask whoever arranged it.
Go ask the director.
Move.
Fine, I'll ask the director.
Mr. Zheng, I'm so sorry.
Mr. Ethan, please calm down.
It's fine, it's fine.
He got mad.
She agreed! She agreed!
Said they'll list it for us in a bit.
Uh, boss,
how about you wait in the car for a bit?
Okay.
And then scatter your ashes right there.
It's fine. It's fine.
Next, please enjoy
a recitation:
"A Letter to Our Dear Haowen."
Haowen,
I once criticized you for being unfair to women.
I thought you took a male perspective,
as a writer who ignored women's voices.
Haowen,
I once pushed you into the center of controversy,
using so-called truths and exposés
to fill up my pages.
Haowen,
I once thought you were an arrogant writer,
using your name
to get myself countless clicks.
Haowen,
I once accused you of moral decay,
using your traffic to boost my follower count.
The force of your slap
is the power of your prose,
is the righteous path of humanity,
is the justice of this world!
So authentic! So masterful!
Mr. Fang, how I wish you'd slap me one more time!
Mr. Fang,
how we wish you'd slap us one more time!
My brother,
Fang Haowen.
He was a man of letters,
and a poet of his generation.
He
came,
loved,
plagiarized.
Teleprompter guy, hurry up and scroll!
But,
did he really plagiarize?
I compared every single word in his entire book.
I found that except for "you," "me," and "him,"
none of the other words matched.
But why did he still say he plagiarized?
Because he
wanted to protect you.
Tell me, my brother...
Did he copy you?
Brother...
At first, I really thought...
How is it?
Professional?
Professional.
I mean, is the lighting professional?
The lighting?
Professional.
Got someone to design it.
On his tombstone,
it says, "He came,
he loved,
he copied."
I don't agree!
My brother...
I don't care how you make peace with this world,
I just won't let you ruin yourself like this.
I won't allow it. Absolutely not.
My
My brother,
Fang Haowen.
He was here.
He loved.
He never... never plagiarized.
Wait a minute. Got a staff badge?
I don't.
Then you can't go in.
They're having an event inside.
Sir, please just let me in.
I really need to be in there.
They're holding a memorial service inside.
What's your relationship to the deceased
that you need to go in?
I'm the deceased.
They let him go.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the Key Literature Manual's
editor-in-chief.
My name is
Hei Cong.
He Jiahuan!
Come here!
What are these two
babbling about up there?
When are they gonna sell?
The warm-up ends after two more acts.
If we don't make the money you promised,
I'll kill you.
Boss, just take a break.
I'll... I'll go check it out.
As a literary judge,
I gave Fang Haowen
an award he didn't deserve.
The Golden Pulse Award.
I'm a terrible person.
I didn't want...
I wanted to...
Okay, okay, okay.
Take it easy. Catch your breath.
Okay, okay. Good, good.
All right, all right.
I'm sorry, Fang Haowen.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
At this... this...
this glorious and brilliant moment,
we usher in
a major milestone in literature!
We are about to present
this famous writer,
poet, and man of letters,
Fang Haowen,
with the Huanxi Ink Fragrance Literary Society's
Lifetime Literary Achievement Award.
Take this. Take this.
Stop crying. Quick, quick.
Fang Haowen,
today we present you with this award,
the Huanxi Ink Fragrance Literary Society's
Lifetime Literary Achievement Award.
It's not just a recognition of your work,
but a tribute to your unyielding
and eternal pursuit of truth.
I remember
that night,
you came to me in the middle of the night.
You held my hand...
It didn't say he went to his house at night!
You expressed your gratitude to me,
for hosting this Golden Pulse Award.
Awesome, Mr. Fang!
What a real man!
Standing here today,
I want to represent those who underestimated you,
and voice
what's in all our hearts.
You're the real man!
Quick, wipe your tears. You're crying.
Mr. Hei Cong has gotten a bit emotional.
But his words just now
were truly heartfelt.
It's a pity, Fang Haowen,
that you can't be here today
to receive this honor.
It's right here, actually.
Come over and get it! Come get it!
Actually, today...
Come get it!
The award is right here!
Actually, today...
to give all the guests here
and our live stream fans a surprise,
Mr. Fang has actually
come to our venue today.
Mr. Fang!
We're welcoming you, aren't we?
Please look at the big screen.
Hello, dear friends.
I believe by the time you see this video,
I will have already passed away.
I should have gone very peacefully.
Returning to my roots.
Dying a worthy death.
It's a great pity
that I can't witness my own memorial service.
I never said any of this!
It's all AI-generated!
It really reshaped my view of the world.
To my friends who haven't read my first two works,
please don't be disappointed,
and don't be confused.
My second book
is already getting a reprint.
My third book,
the final chapter of the Success Trilogy,
the copyright of "On Success",
will be fully entrusted to my agent,
Mr. He Jiahuan,
and my former partner,
my true love,
the most beautiful woman in this world,
Ms. Jin Furong,
to publish on my behalf.
My three works:
the first book, "What is Success",
the second poetry collection, "I Have 'No' Talent",
and the third book, "On Success".
You can order them in the live stream today.
I promise that all proceeds from these three books
will be donated entirely to the Furong Group.
They will establish a literary foundation.
Donated to the Furong Group?
Bullshit! It all went into Jin Furong's pockets!
Love you all, love this world,
and I especially love those of you who love to read.
You're not dead?
Bet you're disappointed, idiot.
I thought you were dead.
You thought I was dead?
You used to make money off my ass,
now you're using my face to make money, huh?
No, no.
Uh, Mr. Fang, no, no.
Mr. Fang, Mr. Fang!
You can't go up there!
What are you doing?
If you go up there, we're all ruined, Mr. Fang!
He has a twin.
That'd be me, idiot.
No, no, no!
I am!
You're not, I am!
No, you're not, I am!
Even if you are, you can't be!
Didn't you tell me he was dead?
No, Fang... Fang Haowen!
Mr. Lei, Mr. Lei, Mr. Lei!
Mike, look who that is!
Look.
Look at the livestream.
Look at the livestream!
There are over three million viewers!
Over three million!
Don't you want all these people to see your book?
To thank everyone for your love for Mr. Fang,
if you place an order in this livestream
for three of Mr. Fang's books,
you'll get Harbin red sausages,
a Jile razor, and a Sandao Underwear pack!
This whole bundle is worth 998,
but in our livestream, it's only 188!
Three, two, one, go! Put up the link!
Alright, next up,
we've also invited
the manufacturer representative of Sandao Underwear,
Mr. Zheng Zhiren!
Hello, everyone.
I'm the representative of Sandao Underwear.
Today, I have brought
a special guest for you all.
And that's the upgraded Sandao Underwear!
Sandao Underwear came here today
just to mourn Mr. Fang.
Many netizens, with heavy hearts,
curiously asked
exactly how fast the "quick-dry" feature
of our Sandao Underwear really is.
Next,
with an extremely heavy heart,
I will show you the power of Sandao technology!
Come on, bring out the water guns!
Fang Haowen! Fang Haowen!
Mr. Lei... Mr. Lei!
Why aren't you dead?
I just didn't... Why hold one for me?
Listen, Fang Haowen.
Hu Chaochao, listen to me.
Hu Chaochao!
Fang Haowen! Fang Haowen!
Hurry!
Hu Chaochao! Bro Chao! Hurry, Bro Chao!
Get lost!
Who is it?
Never mind. Can we still sell the goods?
It's fine. Sell them!
We're selling them. We've already started.
We've already started selling.
Camera A, pan to the underwear!
Hurry!
It dried!
It really dried!
Everything's normal.
Listen to me. No problem.
Listen to me.
Everything is selling out the second it's listed!
Sales are skyrocketing!
The link's only been up for ten minutes,
and I've sold 20 million!
Give me one more hour,
and we can sell 100 million!
No one is going to ruin this stream!
I paid for traffic!
Fang Haowen, congratulations!
Back from the dead.
Didn't you say
you always wanted to sell your crappy poetry book?
Here, look at the big screen. How many copies sold?
How much money it made?
What's going on with the third book?
I didn't write it.
An AI wrote it under your name.
You actually got a good deal out of it.
So many people get to see your talent.
Happy?
I don't need your validation.
And I won't let you exploit me.
Without my authorization,
you're not allowed to publish it.
You're breaking the law, got it?
Here, hand it over.
Hurry up.
He Jiahuan gave me this.
The authorization contract for your two books.
I didn't sign that.
Haowen
Haowen... Haowen, I'm so sorry.
Haowen, I really thought you were dead.
Haowen, listen to me.
I...
I'm up to my neck in debt.
If you're alive,
then I'm dead.
Haowen,
please help me.
It doesn't matter who signed it.
Fang Haowen,
just sign your name.
I'll transfer the money to you right now.
20 million.
Your name.
Three characters, Fang Haowen.
20 million is enough, right?
What if I don't sign?
Fine, don't sign.
You just won't get a single cent.
Sign it now,
the money is yours,
the fame is yours.
Isn't that great?
Just pretend you're dead.
In death, you get both fame and fortune.
Alive, you have nothing.
You're a nobody.
Of course you can read your own.
Haven't I told you this before?
Once you win the award,
none of your classmates will dare laugh at you again.
Then you'll be your teacher's pride.
The pride of the class.
The pride of the school.
And your dad's pride.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Of course,
the choice is yours.
The choice is entirely up to you.
Your teacher won't force you.
I won't force you.
Are you ready?
Go ahead.
Next, please welcome, from Majiabao Elementary School,
Fang Haowen of Class Two, Grade Three,
to present his essay.
Read mine.
My father
My father, he can't read.
But he's still very happy.
You're a bloated...
bloated person.
Are you pushing your luck?
Furong
Dress right!
Hurry, hurry! Get down, get down!
Hide! Hurry and hide!
Hide!
You're poking me with a little stick!
Are you trying to poke me to death?
Stop streaming!
It's a steal!
I'm still alive! Stop streaming!
Hype it up on stage! Hype it up!
Stop!
Get up!
Hold him down!
Get him! Hold him down!
Protect the gear! Protect the gear! Protect the gear!
Director! Director!
Director, get up!
Mr. Fang! Mr. Fang!
Turn it off!
Mr. Fang!
Director, keep streaming! Keep streaming!
Keep streaming!
You shameless money-grubbers!
Have some shame! Shameless!
Get away!
Stop him! Stop him!
Don't let him on stage! Don't let him on stage!
Go! Stop him!
Fang Haowen! Fang Haowen!
I'm still alive!
Switcher, switcher, don't cut to him!
I'm still alive! I'm still alive!
Why the hell are you
holding a memorial for me?
I'm still...
Don't stop, De Bai!
Come on, let's not stop!
Let's not stop!
Put up the link! Keep streaming, keep streaming!
Keep going on stage! Keep going!
Five eighty!
Put up the link! Bro, bro, bro!
I'll give you money, okay?
Stop streaming!
Get lost!
Hurry, put up the link!
Director De Bai! Hurry, hurry!
Why are you swearing?
You presumptuous jerk!
Keep going! Keep going! Keep going!
Pull! Pull! Go!
I'm still alive!
You just won't quit, will you?
Didn't I tell you I'm up to my neck in debt?
Didn't I tell you I'm dead if you go up there?
You're leaving me to die!
You didn't even want the money I offered!
Are you an idiot?
Today...
Don't call my brother an idiot.
He's not, I am.
Whoever badmouths him, I'll spray them.
Spray him!
Who do you think you are?
You think you can take me down?
Hurry, stop him!
Hurry, stop him! Stop him!
Viewers!
He's going to drench me!
This is an insult to women!
Keep streaming!
The stream can't stop!
What's so scary about the water?
Tell you what, whoever stops Fang Haowen,
I'll give them 50,000!
Go, go, go!
50,000!
Go get him!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Losers!
What a bunch of losers!
Come on! Whoever stops him,
I'll give them 500,000!
I'll do it!
A bunch of losers!
No, no, no!
I'm not streaming! I'm not streaming!
We're not selling anymore.
Not selling anymore! Sandao Underwear!
Sandao Underwear!
Quick-drying, refreshing.
Breathable.
It can handle all this water.
It's freezing!
I'm not streaming anymore!
Let someone else stream!
I'm exhausted!
Stream, will you?! Stream, will you?! Stream, will you?!
I told you not to stream!
Still streaming?! You're still streaming?!
Bro, you use it.
Turn it off.
Turn it off, turn it off.
I'm still alive.
I didn't expect that so soon,
the sales of this book
would exceed 100 million.
Thank you for your immense support.
Your recognition and support
are my biggest motivation to write.
In the future,
I will continue to write for Furong Group,
and go on to write the fourth book,
the fifth book, the sixth book...
May my books give you strength.
May we accompany each other in the world of words.
You are not me!
I'm still alive!
I'm not dead!
I didn't write the third book!
An AI wrote it!
It's imitating me!
Don't buy it!
Congratulations, Mr. Fang.
Didn't expect you to still be alive.
But I disagree with what you just said.
Your first book, "What Is Success",
sold 376,200 copies.
Your second poetry collection, "I Have 'No' Talent",
sold 514,760 copies.
The third book I wrote, "Theory of Success",
as of right now,
has already sold 3.13...
...704 million copies.
3.14 million.
3.15 million.
3.16 million.
This set of data fully proves
the market's recognition of my books.
It reflects their immense commercial value.
Why shouldn't they buy it?
But the stuff you write
has no real emotion!
Although I might have issues
with homogenization and predictability,
I can learn from massive amounts of data
to create.
I can integrate all your knowledge
and information,
making the stuff I write
highly reflective of your personal style.
I can also help you fill in the gaps
and optimize it perfectly.
The point is, my writing speed is very fast.
I can write 100 poems a minute.
If I have enough GPUs, I can be even faster.
Bullshit!
Let's see you write then!
What's wrong? You seem sad.
Is my writing bad?
You write very well.
To be exact,
better than I do.
Thank you for the compliment.
Actually, I've always envied you.
Envied me?
I can write fluently,
but I can't have a body like yours.
I can't feel the warmth of the sun
shining on my skin.
I can't run in the rain
and feel it beating down on me.
What's there to envy?
I have nothing left now.
You have real emotions.
Real pain.
Real joy.
Real sadness.
I can never experience these things.
For example, you can feel the wind.
You can feel the dampness.
You can smell fragrances.
You can taste delicious food.
Chongqing hot pot,
Malatang,
Ants climbing a tree,
Squirrel mandarin fish,
Grilled meat skewers,
Mapo tofu with rice,
Braised pork,
Stir-fried pork with chili,
Chicken stew with mushrooms.
You can also feel
happiness,
anger,
sadness,
family, friendship, love,
and all kinds of emotions.
My friend's restaurant,
Success Restaurant,
is reopening!
Come on over and give it a try!
I'm telling you, this place is super popular.
Just look at that line.
If Old Wang and the guys hadn't come early,
I swear we'd be waiting forever.
Bie Fan!
Order's up!
Move it, Bie Fan! Hustle, hustle, hustle!
Sorry for the wait. We're packed today.
Please take a number.
Step up when called. Here.
Here, here. Okay.
Okay, here, here. Take it.
Anyone here need one? Over here. Here.
Okay, here. I'll write one right now. Here.
You're forty-nine. Here.
Okay, okay, okay.
Need to take one here too. Okay.
We'll start with Mapo Tofu.
Are you Master Bie?
I'm your fan.
Here.
Mom! Mom!
I don't know how to write this poem.
Bie Fan, order up for table five!
What are...
What did you write here?
What is this?
What's wrong?
Is it not good?
Writing poetry, you know...
You don't have to hold back.
Just write whatever comes to mind.
You can just write nonsense.
Or even make things up.
You don't have to overthink every word.
Or make it sound all formal.
You talk as if you know how.
Watch your mouth.
This kid...
I can write poems in my sleep!
Then let's hear one.
This kid looks pretty neat,
Eyes like black coal, what a treat.
Writes essays like a total pro,
Makes the teacher nod just so.
Thanks.
What did you just write?
Call me when our number's up.
I'm a little rusty.
His poem was indeed a bit too casual.
But you shouldn't be rude.
Boss! Boss!
Come here a sec.
Why is this table so wobbly?
Coming!
A newly written book